Bikash Panta

Tech Enthusiast

+977-9808123456

bikashpanta51@gmail.com

Pittwater Road, DY, Australia

bikashpanta.github.io/Portfolio/



About me

I have a passion for Computers and enjoy playing with codes.I am learning web development and have worked on various projects in the past.I am skilled in HTML, CSS and JS and always strive to stay updated with the latest industry trends.

Experience

• Computer Teacher

Sunrise Secondary School

Jan 2021 - May 2022

In my role as a computer teacher, I effectively designed and implemented engaging lesson plans to cater to students with varying levels of technical proficiency, fostering a positive learning environment.

Inventory Manager

Urbar Nepal

Feb 2022 - June 2022

Experienced inventory manager proficient in optimizing stock levels, streamlining supply chain operations, and driving cost savings. Strong record-keeping and cross-functional collaboration skills for seamless inventory management.

Education

• **+2** Loyola College 2019-2021

• Bachelor's Wentworth Institute Current

Skills

Organized Critical thinking Teamwork

Communication Resilience Meeting deadlines

Reference

Ramesh Prasai